<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    //Appetizer
    <string name="fried_calamari">Fried Calamari</string>
    <string name="appetizer_type">Appetizer</string>
    <string name="appetizer_imageURL">R.drawable.fried_calamari</string>

    <string name="appetizer_ingredients">
        8-12 oz cleaned squid and tentacles,\n
        1 large egg, beaten, \n
        4 oz all-purpose flour, \n
        2 oz cornstarch, \n
        1/8 teaspoon salt, \n
        3 dashes cayenne pepper, \n
        oil, for deep drying, \n
        bottled tomato sauce or pasta sauce, for dipping, \n
        chopped parsley, for garnishing
    </string>
    <string name="appetizer_steps">
        1. Cut the tubes of cleaned squid into 1/2-inch ring.\n
        2. Transfer the squid to a big bowl with a beaten egg. Stir to mix well.\n
        3. In another big bowl, combine the all purpose flour, cornstarch, salt and cayenne pepper. \n
           Stir to mix well. Working in small batches, drop some squid into the flour mixture. \n
           Coat well and transfer the squid out to a strainer. Repeat until all squid are nicely coated with the flour mixture. \n
           Gently shake the strainer with squid to remove excess flour.\n
        4. Heat up a skillet with 1-inch oil on high heat. \n
           When the oil is heated, deep fry the squid until they turn light brown in color. \n
           Remove the squid from oil and drain on paper towels. \n
        5. Garnish the squid with parsley, serve warm with tomato sauce.
    </string>

    //Main
    <string name="spaghet">Spaghetti Carbonara</string>
    <string name="main_type">Main Dish</string>
    <string name="main_imageURL">R.drawable.spaghet</string>
    <string name="main_ingredients">
        8 ounces spaghetti, \n
        2 large eggs, \n
        1/2 cup freshly grated Parmesan, \n
        4 slices bacon, diced, \n
        4 cloves garlic, minced, \n
        Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste, \n
        2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley leaves
    </string>
    <string name="main_steps">
        1. In a large pot of boiling salted water, cook pasta according to package instructions; reserve 1/2 cup water and drain well. \n
        2. In a small bowl, whisk together eggs and Parmesan; set aside. \n
        3. Heat a large skillet over medium high heat. Add bacon and cook until brown and crispy, about 6-8 minutes; reserve excess fat. \n
        4. Stir in garlic until fragrant, about 1 minute. Reduce heat to low. \n
        5. Working quickly, stir in pasta and egg mixture, and gently toss to combine; \n
        season with salt and pepper, to taste. Add reserved pasta water, one tablespoon at a time, until desired consistency is reached. \n
        6. Serve immediately, garnished with parsley, if desired.
    </string>

    //Dessert
    <string name="choco_mousse">Chocolate Mousse</string>
    <string name="dessert_type">Dessert</string>
    <string name="dessert_imageURL">R.drawable.chocolate_mousse</string>
    <string name="dessert_ingredients">
       100g classic 74% dark chocolate, chopped, plus extra shards to decorate (optional) \n
        25g butter, cubed \n
        3 large eggs, separated \n
        2 tbsp caster sugar \n
        2 tbsp whipping cream (optional)
    </string>
    <string name="dessert_steps">
        1. Put the chocolate, butter and 75ml warm water (see tip, below) in a heatproof bowl set over a pan of barely simmering water. \n
           Push the chocolate and butter gently into the warm water with a wooden spoon to help it melt, but avoid stirring too much. \n
           Once three-quarters of the butter and chocolate is melted, remove the bowl from the heat. \n
           Stir until melted, smooth and glossy. Set aside until lukewarm. \n

        2. Working quickly, use a spatula to stir the egg yolks into the chocolate mixture, one at a time. \n
           In a separate bowl, use an electric whisk to whip the egg whites to soft peaks, then gradually add the sugar, whisking, until stiff peaks form. \n

        3. Gently fold about a fifth of the egg whites into the chocolate mixture, then fold in the rest, being careful not to knock out the air bubbles. \n
           Pour into wine or dessert glasses, cover with clingfilm and chill overnight to set. \n

        4. When ready to serve, whip the cream (if using) to soft peaks. Top each glass with a spoonful of cream and decorate with chocolate shards, if you like.
    </string>

</resources>